{
    "subject": "Ferdinand_II_of_Aragon",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Isabella_I_of_Castile",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand II of Aragon was married to Isabella I of Castile.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9626686573028564,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Isabella I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.956615686416626,
            "question": "Was Ferdinand II of Aragon married to a queen from Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9451419115066528,
            "question": "Who was Ferdinand II of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9255402088165283,
            "question": "Who were the spouses of Ferdinand II and Isabella I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9090340733528137,
            "question": "To whom was Isabella I of Castile married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8756360411643982,
            "question": "Name the Queen who was married to Ferdinand II of Aragon."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8332467079162598,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand II of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6309710741043091,
            "question": "What was the name of the king who shared a marriage with Isabella I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.559353768825531,
            "question": "Who ruled alongside Isabella I of Castile?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34732356667518616,
            "question": "Ferdinand II and Isabella I are known for what significant historical event?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand II of Aragon was married to Isabella I of Castile.",
            "html": "yago_26319_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who ruled alongside Isabella I of Castile?",
            "html": "yago_26319_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the king who shared a marriage with Isabella I of Castile?",
            "html": "yago_26319_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Ferdinand II of Aragon's wife?",
            "html": "yago_26319_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26319_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Ferdinand II of Aragon was married to Isabella I of Castile. The documents mention their marriage on October 19th, 1469 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26319/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt), and describe how they united the Kingdoms of Aragon and Castile into one (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26319/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Ferdinand II of Aragon and Isabella I of Castile, confirming that they were indeed married. For instance, multiple sources mention their marriage on October 19th, 1469, which unified the two kingdoms into one."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}